A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - Conservation, 1962-1976; 9; 114.95 Cubic Feet 290 letter document boxes, 9 legal document boxes and 1 legal tall box
    - United States Government, 9
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Background, 1965 (Box 521, Folder 5, Box 522, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Budget (Box 522, Folder 2)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Clippings, 1965 (Box 522, Folder 3-4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Clippings - Richman, 1965 (Box 523, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Congratulatory letters, 1965 (Box 523, Folder 2)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Delegates, 1965 (Box 523, Folder 3)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - H. Diamond Schedule, 1965 (Box 523, Folder 4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Entertainment, 1965 (Box 523, Folder 5)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Follow Up, 1965-1966 (Box 523, Folder 6)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Invitations - General, 1965 (Box 524, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Invitations - A-M, 1965 (Box 524, Folder 2-4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Invitations - N-Z, 1965 (Box 525, Folder 1-2)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Letters of Appreciation, 1965 (Box 525, Folder 3)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Kit, 1965 (Box 525, Folder 4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Meetings, 1965 (Box 525, Folder 5)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Memos, 1965 (Box 525, Folder 6)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Operating Procedure, Program, 1965 (Box 526, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Panel Matters, 1965 (Box 526, Folder 2-3)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Panels, 1964-1965 (Box 526, Folder 4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Panels - Memoranda, 1965 (Box 527, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Printed Material, 1965 (Box 527, Folder 2)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Proceedings Distribution, 1965 (Box 527, Folder 3-7)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Program Planning, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Proposals, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 2)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Public Affairs, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 3)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Recreation Advisory Council, 1964-1965 (Box 528, Folder 4)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Releases, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 5)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Report, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 6)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1965 (Box 528, Folder 7, Box 529, Folder 1)
      - White House Conference on Natural Beauty - William Whyte's Schedule Book, 1965 (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - D-E, 1962-1976; 10; 13.66 Cubic Feet 31 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - D - Miscellaneous, 1962-1976 (Box 529, Folder 3-4)
    - D - Miscellaneous - Dicks, Randall J., 1973-1976 (Box 530, Folder 1)
    - Defense - Military Matters, 1963-1976 (Box 530, Folder 2-3)
    - Defense - Defense Orientation Conference Association (DOCA), 1972-1976 (Box 530, Folder 4)
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z, 1967-1976 (Box 531, Folder 1-4)
    - Defense - Veterans - Navy League of the U.S.A., 1962-1976 (Box 532, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - General Correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 532, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1959-1964 (Box 532, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1969-1973 (Box 533, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Committee for Corporate Support of American Universities, 1962-1967 (Box 533, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Community Service Society - General, 1962-1966 (Box 534, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Community Service Society - Collection, 1961-1965 (Box 534, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Community Service Society - Campaign, 1966 (Box 534, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Ferry Morse Seed Company, 1962-1964 (Box 534, Folder 5, Box 535, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Hills Realty, 1958-1960 (Box 535, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Garenzik Matter, 1959-1975 (Box 535, Folder 3-4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Institute for International Social Research, 1963-1973 (Box 536, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1961-1974 (Box 536, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Appointment of New Director, 1966 (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Finances, 1970-1975 (Box 537, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Finances - Finance Committee Minutes and Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 538, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Finances - C.M. Paget Study, 1970 (Box 538, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Finances - New York City, 1968-1970 (Box 538, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Garage Proposal, 1972 (Box 538, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Board of Trustees - Minutes/Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 539, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - 100 Anniversary, 1966-1970 (Box 539, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Restaurant, 1972 (Box 539, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Procedures for Deaccessioning Art, 1972-1974 (Box 540, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Staff, 1967-1974 (Box 540, Folder 2-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Staff (Box 540, Folder 2a)
      Restricted - Personnel (Kenneth Loughry) - Open in 2038
      Restricted - Personnel (Oscar Muscarella) - Open in 2044
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - NAR Farms, 1962-1966 (Box 541, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - New York Foundation, 1963-1965 (Box 541, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Planned Parenthood - Annual Dinners, 1974-1975 (Box 541, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Planned Parenthood - Commerce and Industry Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Planned Parenthood - Fund Raising Campaign, 1966-1969 (Box 541, Folder 6, Box 542, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Planned Parenthood - General Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 541, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Politics - General, 1958-1966 (Box 542, Folder 2-5, Box 543, Folder 1-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Political Contributions, 1962-1967 (Box 543, Folder 4, Box 544, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Governor's Club, 1966-1967 (Box 544, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - New York City Mayoralty Election, 1961 (Box 544, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - New York Republican State Committee, 1959-1971 (Box 544, Folder 4-5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Republican Dinners, 1959-1965 (Box 544, Folder 6, Box 545, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - DR - New York State Finance Committee, 1966 (Box 545, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Political State Bond Issues, 1960-1962 (Box 545, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Special Gifts Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 545, Folder 4-5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Philip, Sporn, 1962 (Box 545, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - United Republican Finance Committee, 1959-1966 (Box 546, Folder 1-3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - United Republican Finance Committee - Collections, 1959-1961 (Box 546, Folder 4, Box 547, Folder 1-4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - United Republican Finance Committee - Contributions, National and State, 1962-1964 (Box 548, Folder 1-6)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - United Republican Finance Committee - Meetings, 1961-1965 (Box 548, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Pollution, 1965 (Box 549, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Rockefeller Center, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 549, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Columbia Lease, 1959-1961 (Box 549, Folder 3-4, Box 550, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Rock-Hill Uris Corp., 1960-1965 (Box 549, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Rockefeller University, 1960-1965 (Box 549, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - 30 Rockefeller Plaza Associates (Box 550, Folder 1-4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - U.S. Government, General Accounting Office, 1964 (Box 551, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Urban Design Council of the City of New York, 1967-1972 (Box 551, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale General, 1964-1972 (Box 551, Folder 3-4, Box 552, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale Corporation - General, 1959-1972 (Box 552, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Admissions - Lawrence Dunham, 1967-1972 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Performance, 1965-1967 (Box 553, Folder 1-2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Admissions and Scholarship, 1968-1972 (Box 553, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Subcommittee on Admissions, 1965-1972 (Box 553, Folder 4, Box 554, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Aircraft, 1968-1970 (Box 554, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Alumni Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 554, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Alumni Fund, 1961-1972 (Box 554, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Coffin, William Sloan (Rev), 1967-1972 (Box 554, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Convocation, 1968 (Box 554, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Class of 1938, 1938 1961-1972 (Box 554, Folder 7)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finances, 1972 (Box 555, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finances - Budget, 1968-1973 (Box 555, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Deferred Tuition Plan, 1970-1971 (Box 555, Folder 3-4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Engineering and Applied Sciences at Yale, 1967 (Box 555, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Endowment Management and Research Corp., 1968-1972 (Box 556, Folder 1-4, Box 557, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Endowment Management and Research Corp. - Building (Possible Purchase), 1968 (Box 557, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Endowment Funds - Annie Burr Lewis Higgins Trust, 1966-1967 (Box 557, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finance Committee - Meetings, 1967 November 9-1973 March 9 (Box 557, Folder 4, Box 558, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Financial - Omega Fund, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 558, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finances - Sperry and Hutchinson Company, 1971-1972 (Box 558, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finances - Stock Loan Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 558, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Finances - Uniform Management of Institutional Funds Act, 1971-1972 (Box 558, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Library, 1963-1972 (Box 558, Folder 6, Box 559, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - President's Garden, 1965-1966 (Box 559, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Properties, 1967-1972 (Box 559, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Properties - Liggett Building, 1972 (Box 559, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Sheffield Scientific School, 1970 (Box 559, Folder 5)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Social Responsibility, 1969-1972 (Box 559, Folder 6)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - University Council, 1970 (Box 560, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - J. H. Whitney/Undergraduate Housing, 1970-1972 (Box 560, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Women at Yale, 1970-1971 (Box 560, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Yale University - Yale Club, 1970 (Box 560, Folder 4)
    - E - Miscellaneous, 1962-1976 (Box 560, Folder 5)
    - Energy - A-Z (Box 788, Folder 3-5)
    - Expositions (Box 789, Folder 1)
    - Expositions - New York World's Fair (Box 789, Folder 2-3)
    - Expositions - New York World's Fair - A-Z (Box 789, Folder 4)
    - Expositions - New York World's Fair - Hall of Free Enterprise (Box 790, Folder 1)
    - Expositions - New York World's Fair - Printed material (Box 790, Folder 2-3)
  - Economics, 1962-1976; 11; 5.32 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes
    - Economics - A-B, 1962-1976 (Box 561, Folder 1-3)
    - Economics - C-E (Box 562, Folder 1-3)
    - Economics - F-M (Box 563, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - M-N (Box 564, Folder 1-3)
    - Economics - O-Z (Box 565, Folder 1-4)
    - American Business Committee on National Priorities, 1971-1972 (Box 566, Folder 1)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1963-1971 (Box 566, Folder 2-3)
    - Center on Corporate Responsibility, 1972-1975 (Box 566, Folder 4)
    - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1962-1971 (Box 566, Folder 5)
    - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1962-1973 (Box 567, Folder 1)
    - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Contributions (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - Committee for a National Trade Policy - Printed Material (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1964-1974 (Box 567, Folder 4, Box 568, Folder 1)
    - Conference Board (Formerly National Industrial Conference Board), 1968-1973 (Box 568, Folder 2-3)
    - Development Action, Inc., 1971 (Box 568, Folder 4)
    - Council on Economic Priorities, 1971-1976 (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - Labor, 1962-1964 (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Management, 1962-1965 (Box 569, Folder 3)
    - Maine Development Advisory Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 569, Folder 4-5, Box 570, Folder 1-2)
    - Maine Development Advisory Committee - Reception for Governor Curtis of Maine, 1971 April 15 (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1962-1973 (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research - Contributions, 1966-1975 (Box 571, Folder 1)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research - Printed Material, 1970-1972 (Box 571, Folder 2)
    - National Council for Urban Economic Development, 1973-1974 (Box 571, Folder 3)
    - National Council for Urban Economic Development - Printed Material, 1973-1976 (Box 571, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, 1963-1964 (Box 571, Folder 5)
    - Taxes - McLean, Donald H., Jr. - Legislation re: Additional Ten Percent Reduction for Charitable Contributions, 1960-1962 (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - Taxes - Rockefeller, David, 1963 (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Taxes - Tax Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Printed Material, 1976-1977 (Box 572, Folder 4, Box 573, Folder 1)
    - Virgin Islands Government Improvement Project, 1970-1976 (Box 573, Folder 2)
    - Virgin Islands Incentive Study Program, 1972-1974 (Box 573, Folder 3, Box 574, Folder 1-3)
  - Education, 1962-1976; 12; 82.02 Cubic Feet 211 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes
    - Education - A-Z, 1
      - Education - A (Box 574, Folder 4, Box 575, Folder 1-2)
      - Education - B-C (Box 575, Folder 3-4)
      - Education - C (Box 576, Folder 1-3)
      - Education - D-H (Box 577, Folder 1-4)
      - Education - H-Institute (Box 578, Folder 1-3)
      - Education - International-K (Box 579, Folder 1-3)
      - Education - L-N (Box 580, Folder 1-4)
      - Education - O-S (Box 581, Folder 1-4)
      - Education - S-Z (Box 582, Folder 1-4)
      - Adult Education, 1962-1966 (Box 583, Folder 1)
      - American Geographical Society, 1973-1975 (Box 583, Folder 2)
      - American Geographical Society - Printed Material, 1971-1974 (Box 583, Folder 3)
      - American Philosophical Society and Wistar Association (Box 583, Folder 4)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 583, Folder 5)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies - Printed Material, 1974-1976 (Box 584, Folder 1)
      - Berkshire Outdoor Learning District, 1971-1972 (Box 584, Folder 2)
      - Board of Cooperative Educational Services, 1969 (Box 584, Folder 3)
      - Brookings Institution, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 584, Folder 4)
      - Center for American Living Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 584, Folder 5)
      - Centre d'Echanges Technologiques Internationaux, 1964-1967 (Box 584, Folder 6)
      - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1975-1976 (Box 584, Folder 7)
      - Design Science Institute, 1972-1976 (Box 585, Folder 1)
      - Earthwatch, 1974-1976 (Box 585, Folder 2-3, Box 586, Folder 1)
      - Hudson Institute, 1967-1971 (Box 586, Folder 2)
      - Foresta Institute for Ocean and Mountain Studies, 1964-1965 (Box 586, Folder 3)
      - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1968-1972 (Box 586, Folder 4)
      - Institute for Regional Education, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 586, Folder 5)
      - Institute for International Education, 1963-1971 (Box 587, Folder 1)
      - Institute on Man and Science, 1963-1976 (Box 587, Folder 2)
      - Institute of Public Administration, 1962-1965 (Box 587, Folder 3)
      - Institute of Public Administration - Outhwaite Study, 1962-1966 (Box 587, Folder 4)
      - Institute on Man and Science - Printed Material, 1967-1975 (Box 588, Folder 1)
      - Institute on Man and Science - Rockefeller Family, 1965-1972 (Box 588, Folder 2)
      - International Baccalaureate, 1974 (Box 588, Folder 3)
      - International Institute of Differing Civilizations, 1964-1966 (Box 588, Folder 4)
      - Lindisforne Association - Printed Material, 1974-1975 (Box 589, Folder 1)
      - Israel Foundations Trustees, 1976 (Box 589, Folder 2)
      - Motion Pictures (Box 744, Folder 4)
      - National Center for Education in Politics, 1963-1964 (Box 589, Folder 3)
      - National Committee for Citizens in Education, 1963-1976 (Box 589, Folder 4)
      - National Fund for Medical Education, 1967-1970 (Box 589, Folder 5)
      - National Geographic Society, 1966-1976 (Box 590, Folder 1)
      - National Geographic Society - A-Z, 1966-1976 (Box 590, Folder 2-3)
      - National Geographic Society - Committee on Research and Exploration, 1968-1971 (Box 591, Folder 1)
      - National Geographic Society - Finances, 1972-1976 (Box 591, Folder 2-5, Box 592, Folder 1-3)
      - National Geographic Society - Finance Committee Meetings, 1972-1975 (Box 592, Folder 5-6, Box 593, Folder 1-3)
      - National Geographic Society - Minutes/Meetings - Board of Trustees, 1973-1976 (Box 592, Folder 4)
      - National Institute of Social Sciences, 1962-1977 (Box 593, Folder 4)
      - National Institute of Social Sciences - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1975 (Box 593, Folder 5)
      - National Institute of Social Sciences - Rockefeller Family and Rockefeller Brothers Award, 1967 November 28 (Box 594, Folder 1)
      - National Institute of Social Sciences - Rockefeller Family and Rockefeller Brothers Award - Public Relations Material, 1967-1968 (Box 594, Folder 2)
      - Publications (Box 744, Folder 5)
      - Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. (SIECUS), 1967-1976 (Box 594, Folder 3)
      - Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. (SIECUS) - Contributions, 1970-1976 (Box 594, Folder 4)
      - Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. (SIECUS) - Printed Material, 1968-1969 (Box 595, Folder 1)
      - Adlai E. Stevenson Institute of International Affairs, 1966-1967 (Box 595, Folder 2)
      - Southern Highlands Literary Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 595, Folder 3)
      - Task Force on Children Out of School, 1970-1971 (Box 595, Folder 4)
      - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars - Kennan Institute for Advanced Russian Studies, 1973-1976 (Box 596, Folder 1)
      - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, 1967-1976 (Box 596, Folder 2)
      - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution - Printed Material, 1968-1974 (Box 596, Folder 3)
    - Colleges/Universities, 2
      - Colleges/Universities - A, 1962-1976 (Box 597, Folder 1-4, Box 598, Folder 1)
      - Colleges/Universities - B (Box 598, Folder 2-4)
      - Colleges/Universities - B-C (Box 599, Folder 1-4)
      - Colleges/Universities - C (Box 600, Folder 1-3, Box 601, Folder 1-2)
      - Colleges/Universities - D-F (Box 602, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - F-H (Box 603, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - H-I (Box 604, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - J-L (Box 605, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - M (Box 606, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - N-O (Box 607, Folder 1-4)
      - Colleges/Universities - P-S (Box 608, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - S-T (Box 609, Folder 1-4)
      - Colleges/Universities - U-University of, A-C (Box 610, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - University of, D-N (Box 611, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - University of, N-Z (Box 612, Folder 1-3)
      - Colleges/Universities - U-V (Box 612, Folder 4)
      - Colleges/Universities - W-Z (Box 613, Folder 1-2)
      - Air Force Academy Foundation (Box 613, Folder 3)
      - Air University, 1960-1965 (Box 613, Folder 4)
      - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1973 (Box 614, Folder 1)
      - American School of Classical Studies in Athens, 1963-1974 (Box 614, Folder 2)
      - American University in Beirut, 1971-1976 (Box 614, Folder 3)
      - American University in Cairo, 1973-1976 (Box 614, Folder 4)
      - Antioch College, 1967-1971 (Box 614, Folder 5)
      - Bard College, 1967-1971 (Box 614, Folder 6)
      - Bennington College, 1967-1972 (Box 614, Folder 7)
      - Boston University, 1965-1966 (Box 614, Folder 8)
      - Bowdoin College, 1971 (Box 615, Folder 1)
      - Bradford Junior College, 1965-1971 (Box 615, Folder 2)
      - Bradford Junior College - Printed Material, 1965-1968 (Box 615, Folder 3)
      - Brandeis University, 1962-1966 (Box 615, Folder 4)
      - Briarcliff College, 1962-1966 (Box 615, Folder 5)
      - Brown University - Contributions, 1963-1966 (Box 615, Folder 6)
      - Brown University, 1962-1970 (Box 615, Folder 7)
      - Brown University - Printed Material, 1962-1966 (Box 616, Folder 1)
      - Bryn Mawr, 1966-1971 (Box 616, Folder 2)
      - California Institute of Technology, 1962-1973 (Box 616, Folder 3)
      - Cambridge University, 1970-1973 (Box 616, Folder 4)
      - Case Institute of Technology, 1962-1966 (Box 616, Folder 5)
      - Catholic University of Puerto Rico, 1966-1969 (Box 616, Folder 6)
      - City University of New York, 1967-1976 (Box 616, Folder 7)
      - Clark University, 1967-1971 (Box 617, Folder 1)
      - Colby College, 1962-1964 (Box 617, Folder 2)
      - Colgate University, 1963-1966 (Box 617, Folder 3)
      - Colgate University - Festival of the Creative Arts, 1963-1964 (Box 617, Folder 4)
      - Colgate University - Fortnight of Active Arts, 1967-1968 (Box 617, Folder 5)
      - College of Human Services, 1970 (Box 617, Folder 6)
      - College of Idaho, 1967-1970 (Box 617, Folder 7)